{"test_questions": [[{"question": "Needing to using more complicated SQL in database applications is a(n) ________ of normalization.", "opta": "advantage", "optb": "disadvantage", "optc": "either an advantage or disadvantage", "optd": "neither an advantage nor disadvantage", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Eliminating modification anomalies is a(n) ________ of normalization.", "opta": "advantage", "optb": "disadvantage", "optc": "either an advantage or disadvantage", "optd": "neither an advantage nor disadvantage", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Multivalued dependencies should ________ be eliminated.", "opta": "always", "optb": "commonly", "optc": "seldom", "optd": "never", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "When assessing the table structure of an acquired set of tables with data, accessing the validity of possible referential integrity constraints on foreign keys is (part of) the:", "opta": "first step.", "optb": "second step.", "optc": "third step.", "optd": "fourth step.", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Using the SQL GROUP BY phrase with a SELECT statement can help detect which of the following problems?", "opta": "The multivalue, multicolumn problem", "optb": "The inconsistent values problem", "optc": "The missing values problem", "optd": "The general-purpose remarks column problem", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "When assessing the table structure of an acquired set of tables with data, determining foreign keys is (part of) the:", "opta": "first step.", "optb": "second step.", "optc": "third step.", "optd": "fourth step.", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Creating a read-only database is a task that is ________ assigned to beginning database professionals.", "opta": "always", "optb": "commonly", "optc": "seldom", "optd": "never", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Each answer below shows example data from a table. Which answer is an example of the general-purpose remarks column problem?", "opta": "Three columns have the values 534-2435, 534-7867, and 546-2356 in the same row.", "optb": "Three rows have the values Brown Small Chair, Small Chair Brown, and Small Brown Chair in the same column.", "optc": "Three rows have the values Brown, NULL, and Blue in the same column.", "optd": "One row has the value \"He is interested in a Silver Porsche from the years 1978-1988\" in a column.", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "For a number of reasons, normalizations is not often an advantage for a(n) ________ database.", "opta": "read-only", "optb": "updateable", "optc": "either a read-only or an updateable", "optd": "None of the above is correct.", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Most of the time, modification anomalies are serious enough that tables should be normalized into:", "opta": "1NF.", "optb": "2NF.", "optc": "3NF.", "optd": "BCNF.", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Each answer below shows example data from a table. Which answer is an example of the missing values problem?", "opta": "Three columns have the values 534-2435, 534-7867, and 546-2356 in the same row.", "optb": "Three rows have the values Brown Small Chair, Small Chair Brown, and Small Brown Chair in the same column.", "optc": "Three rows have the values Brown, NULL, and Blue in the same column.", "optd": "One row has the value \"He is interested in a Silver Porsche from the years 1978-1988\" in a column.", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "When assessing the table structure of an acquired set of tables with data, determining functional dependencies is (part of) the:", "opta": "first step.", "optb": "second step.", "optc": "third step.", "optd": "fourth step.", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Each answer below shows example data from a table. Which answer is an example of the multivalue, multicolumn problem?", "opta": "Three columns have the values 534-2435, 534-7867, and 546-2356 in the same row.", "optb": "Three rows have the values Brown Small Chair, Small Chair Brown, and Small Brown Chair in the same column.", "optc": "Three rows have the values Brown, NULL, and Blue in the same column.", "optd": "One row has the value \"He is interested in a Silver Porsche from the years 1978-1988\" in a column.", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "When assessing the table structure of an acquired set of tables with data, counting the number of table rows is (part of) the:", "opta": "first step.", "optb": "second step.", "optc": "third step.", "optd": "fourth step.", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "If a table has been normalized so that all determinants are candidate keys, then that table is in:", "opta": "1NF.", "optb": "2NF.", "optc": "3NF.", "optd": "BCNF.", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Read-only databases are ________ updated.", "opta": "always", "optb": "commonly", "optc": "seldom", "optd": "never", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Needing to assess the validity of assumed referential integrity constraints on foreign keys is a(n) ________ of normalization.", "opta": "advantage", "optb": "disadvantage", "optc": "either an advantage or disadvantage", "optd": "neither an advantage nor disadvantage", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "When assessing the table structure of an acquired set of tables with data, determining primary keys is (part of) the:", "opta": "first step.", "optb": "second step.", "optc": "third step.", "optd": "fourth step.", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Normalization ________ data duplication.", "opta": "eliminates", "optb": "reduces", "optc": "increases", "optd": "maximizes", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Each answer below shows example data from a table. Which answer is an example of the inconsistent values problem?", "opta": "Three columns have the values 534-2435, 534-7867, and 546-2356 in the same row.", "optb": "Three rows have the values Brown Small Chair, Small Chair Brown, and Small Brown Chair in the same column.", "optc": "Three rows have the values Brown, NULL, and Blue in the same column.", "optd": "One row has the value \"He is interested in a Silver Porsche from the years 1978-1988\" in a column.", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}]]}